Preliminary Inventory of the Committee on the Present Danger records
Hoover Institution Archives
- "The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance-The Price of Being Number 2," 1984, Title will become "Can America Catch Up?" material (see also boxes 152-357) (Folder 493)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance brochure, loose material, 1984 (Folder 494)